### Analytics

### Databases

### Insights

### Pricing

### Help Center

### Community, feedback, bug reporting

VG INSIGHTS PRIVACY POLICY
==========================

We at VG Insights are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. This Privacy Policy governs our data collection, processing and usage practices. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. By using our website, client portal, or Subscription Service, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not use these services.

The Information That VG Insights Collects
-----------------------------------------

You are free to explore VGInsights.com without providing any Personal Information about yourself. When you register as a user, or download a report, we request that you provide Personal Information about yourself and we may collect Navigational Information.

Personal Information refers to any information that you voluntarily submit to us and that identifies you personally, including contact information, such as your name, email address, company name, address, phone number. This can also include information about any transactions, both free and paid, that you enter into on the websites, and information about you that is available on the internet, such as from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and Google.

Navigational Information refers to information about your visits to our website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit, pages viewed, and device information. This is collected through the use “cookies”, which help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time.

Cookies are stored on your individual device and you have full control over their use. You may deactivate or restrict the transmission of cookies by changing the settings of your web browser. Cookies that are already stored may be deleted at any time.

How We Use Information We Collect on the Platform
-------------------------------------------------

We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. Registered customers are obligated through our agreements with them to comply with this Privacy Policy. We will NEVER sell your Personal Information to any third party.

In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to: (a) improve your browsing experience (b) send information to you which we think may be of interest to you by email (c) send you marketing communications relating to our business.

We use Navigational Information to operate and improve the website and the our service. We may also use Navigational Information alone or in combination with Personal Information to provide you with personalized information about VG Insights.

If you give us credit card information, we use it solely to check your financial qualifications and collect payment from you. We use a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use the information you provide except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf.

Security of Your Personal Information
-------------------------------------

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When sensitive Personal Information (such as a credit card number and/or geo-location data) is collected on our Websites and/or transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Retention of Personal Information
---------------------------------

We retain Personal Information that you provide as long as we consider it potentially useful in contacting you about our services, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements, and then we securely delete the information. We will delete this information from the servers at an earlier date if you so request, as described in “Opting Out and Unsubscribing” below.

Use of Publicly Available Player Data
-------------------------------------

We may collect and process data from publicly accessible player profiles on third party platforms. This data is used exclusively in an aggregated and anonymized manner to analyze game ownership and estimate sales figures. No personally identifiable information is collected, stored, or shared. Our use of this data complies with applicable laws and respects the privacy settings chosen by platform users. If you have any questions about how we use public data, please contact us.

Opting Out and Unsubscribing
----------------------------

Upon request, VG Insights will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personal Information. You can review, update, or correct this Personal Information by contacting us at [support@vginsights.com](mailto:support@vginsights.com). To opt-out of receiving our newsletters, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of our emails or contact us at the above email address. We will respond to your request within 30 days, but usually in a day or two. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with us.

© 2024

Video Game Insights

Please contact us at support@vginsights.com with any issues or feedback.

Please enable JavaScript to continue using this application.
